question_data = [
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "In the Super Mario series, the character Pauline is a Princess like Princess Peach.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "Sonic the Hedgehog 2 originally was going to have a time travel system.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "In the S.T.A.L.K.E.R. series, the Freedom faction wishes to destroy the supernatural area known as the Zone.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "Tony Hawk's extreme sports videogames revolve around performing professional BMX tricks.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "Big the Cat is a playable character in Sonic Generations.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "In Kingdom Hearts the Paopu fruit is said to intertwine the destinies for two people forever.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "Nintendo's Luigi was originally just called Green Mario?",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "Each piece in Tetris is called a tetris.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "In Sonic Adventure, you are able to transform into Super Sonic at will after completing the main story.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "The names of Tom Nook's cousins in the Animal Crossing franchise are named Timmy and Jimmy.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    }
  ]
